Sofia Grytsenko

USER EXPERIENCE DESIGNER

(201) 417-3350

sofiagry1@gmail.com

Rochester, NY

https://people.rit.edu/sdg3149/portfolio/

OBJECTIVE

A UX designer with four years of experience in user flows, wire-framing, interaction design, and prototyping in Figma and all Adobe Creative Cloud applications. A proven track record of designing creative, usable web and mobile applications.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science (B.S)

Human-Centered Computing

Web Development & Psychology Minor

3.8 GPA - May 2023

Rochester Institute of Technology

New York, NY

EXPERIENCE

May 2022- Aug 2022

CONTENT CREATION INTERN | Windstream Communications, Little Rock, AR

- Worked on 10+ technical informational videos using Adobe Premiere Pro and After Effects
- Repurposed and optimized the results of 6 sprints for use in different mediums.
- Played an instrumental role in creative planning and 30+ review sessions.
- Collaborated with my supervisor to elevate quality of 10+ videos.
- Utilized exceptional writing, editing and video-making skills to produce engaging and error-free content for 100s of non-technical employees.

July 2021 - Dec 2021 UX DESIGN INTERN | Akoya LLC, Boston, MA

- Created 50+ interactive designs for complex web applications by way of user flow diagrams, site maps, and interactive prototypes in Figma.
- Worked within a design team to create 2 high-fidelity prototypes with 20+ screens.
- Designed a widget dashboard for Akoya's apps to solve 80% of users' FAQs.
- Designed 5 new features for the dashboard.
- Conducted 6 UX research studies by interactively creating and testing high and low fidelity prototypes.

Jan 2021 - Present

TEACHING ASSISTANT | Rochester Institute of Technology, Rochester, NY

- Assisted teachers with classroom management and documentation with up to 100 students.
- Maintained a positive learning environment with the subjects Java, HTML, and CSS with groups of 30 students at a time.

SKILLS

- Figma, Adobe: Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign,
 Premiere Pro, After Effects
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery

Java, MySQL, PHP, C#

 Interaction Design, Software Infrastructure, Project Management